aspose.com 2010-06-10

# Privacy Policy - Corporate - Aspose

| 

|   
---  

This web site is maintained by Aspose Pty Ltd, Suite 163, 79 Longueville Road, Lane Cove, NSW, 2066, Australia. By accessing or using the Aspose.com Web site, you agree to the terms of the Aspose Online Privacy Policy, as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site.

As of May 15, 2007, Aspose Pty Ltd has updated its Privacy Policy in order to give you a better understanding of its Privacy Policy and Practices. If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us at privacy@aspose.com.  

## Overview  

Aspose takes online security very seriously and is committed to protecting your privacy. In order to access some Aspose services you will be asked to provide personal identification information ("Personal Information"). Personal Information includes any information that may be used to identify you, such as: first and last name, home or other physical address, telephone numbers, e-mail addresses, or other contact information that is provided to us by you, or any other party. In general, you may visit Aspose's web pages without disclosing to us who you are and without revealing any Personal Information about yourself.

You should be aware though, that if you choose to provide us with your Personal Information, we may transfer such information, within Aspose or to Aspose's third party service providers, across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world, subject to the limitations of this Privacy Policy.

Aspose strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, Aspose intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Online Privacy Policy.  

## Choice  

You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to Aspose. However, when you engage in certain activities on this site, such as ordering products, downloading software, or entering contests, Aspose may require that you provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is entirely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, Aspose may require that you provide certain personal information, such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, and other personal identifying information.  

## Cookies and other tracking technologies  

When you visit Aspose.com, you may surf the site anonymously and access important information without revealing your identity. In order to analyze and improve our site, we use "cookies" to track your visit. A cookie is small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a Web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. “Cookies” cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, therefore allowing you to decide whether or not to accept it. (For some Web pages that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies will not be able to access such pages.)

While Aspose uses cookies to track your visit to Aspose.com, and our Web servers automatically log the IP/Internet address of your computer, this information does not identify you personally and you remain anonymous unless you have otherwise provide Aspose with Personal Information.  

## Newsletters  

From time to time Aspose will provide information to their customers in the form of electronic newsletters. When you subscribe to the Aspose.com newsletter you will be added to our mailing list and will receive announcements and information about Aspose. The announcements and information will come from Aspose, not from third parties. It will be emailed directly to the email address that you provide when you subscribe. If you no longer wish to receive newsletters from us in the future, you can sign-in aspose.com and then unsubscribe at the following URL: <http://www.aspose.com/community/user/editprofile.aspx>  

## Forums  

You may provide Personal Information through your participation in forums on Aspose.com. That information is public and immediately available to anyone who has access to this site; it is not private. This Privacy Policy does not apply to such information.  

## Security  

Wherever your Personal Information may be held by Aspose or by a third party on Aspose’s behalf, reasonable and appropriate precautions, such as encryption, firewalls and like technologies, are and will be implemented to protect such Personal Information from loss, misuse or unauthorized access.  

## Access/Accuracy  

To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, Aspose wishes to maintain it accurately and updated. Where we collect Personal Information from you, our goal is to provide a means of contacting Aspose should you need to access, update or correct that Information. If for any reason you desire to review such information, please contact us at privacy@aspose.com and we will make reasonable efforts to promptly provide you with such information. Further, if you notify us that such information is incorrect, or you wish to have such information removed, we will correct, amend, or delete your Personal Information as soon as practicable.  

## Third party services  

In the interest of providing better service to its customers, Aspose is represented in Australia and in some foreign countries by authorized distributors and resellers who provide marketing, sales, and support services to Aspose customers. When you submit personal information to Aspose, you understand and agree that Aspose may allow Aspose’s authorized distributors and resellers access to your customer profile for the exclusive purpose of providing you with marketing, sales, and support services for Aspose products.

Your personal information will not be leased, sold, rented or otherwise made available to any other third party except to the extent necessary to comply with applicable laws, police investigations, or in legal proceedings where such information is relevant. Occasionally, Aspose allows access to database information to bonded mailing houses only for the purpose of allowing for the printing of mailing labels that are used for Aspose's own direct mail and promotional purposes. In those instances, the third party is strictly bound by these terms.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, you hereby agree that Aspose may assign, sell, license, or otherwise transfer to a third party, your name, address, email address, member name and any other personal information in connection with an assignment, sale, joint venture, or other transfer or disposition of a material portion or essentially all of the assets or stock of Aspose or its affiliated entities.  

## Children's privacy  

Aspose.com is not designed nor structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age. If we are made aware that information is or has been submitted by or collected from a child under the age of thirteen, we will promptly delete this information.  

## Sensitive information  

We do not collect Sensitive Information such as medical, health, racial, ethnic, political, religious, philosophic, union membership or sexual orientation information. If we are made aware that we have received such information, we will promptly proceed to its deletion.  

## Your consent  

By using this web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to Aspose's processing of Personal Information for the purposes outlined above. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time.
